ADRIENNE LEE

FULL STACK DEVELOPER

adriennelee.dev

adrienneklee@gmail.com Hamilton, ON







PERSONAL PROFILE

I am a Full Stack Developer currently working as the lead in-house Web Developer for Point Blank, Canada's largest progressive creative agency. My passion for tech is bolstered by my experience in corporate social responsibility and has fuelled me in developing accessible, meaningful and responsive web applications.

WEB DEV SKILLS

- HTML5
- CSS3/SCSS
- Javascript
- ¡Query
- React
- Ruby on Rails
- PHP

- Firebase
- WordPress
- Paired/Group Programming
- Accessibility Standards
- Google Analytics

EDUCATION

Juno College of Technology

Web Development Immersive Oct 2021 - December 2021 Intermediate Javascript Intro to Web Development

Toronto Metropolitan University

Masters of Environmental Applied Science and Management

Sept 2009 - May 2011

McMaster University

Bachelors of Biochemistry and Biomedical Science

Sept 2004 - May 2007

FEATURED PROJECTS

Guess Who Ghibli

HTML5 | SASS | Javascript | REST APIs **Paired Programming**

A web application made with Vanilla JS. Users are provided clues to guess randomly generated characters from the magical world of Studio Ghibli. Live Link | GitHub Repo

Safe Spaces Toronto

HTML3 and CSS3 | React | REST APIs | Firebase

An application built with React that seeks to provide safe restroom access for gender nonconforming individuals. Safe Spaces utilizes data from the Refuge Washroom API, Navigator Geolocation, and Firebase. Live Link | GitHub Repo

Sun Run

HTML5 | CSS3 | React | REST APIs | Firebase **Team Programming**

A team project built with React, Sun Run utilizes multiple APIs and Firebase persistence. Sun Run allows users to plan runs based on dates, sunrise/set times, distance, and pace. Live Link | GitHub Repo

EXPERIENCE

WEB DEVELOPER

Point Blank Creative (Jan 2022 - Present)

As Point Blanks sole in-house Developer, I am responsible for:

- Building pixel-perfect, responsive, accessible, front-end web products using HTML + CSS, JS, PHP, and Ruby on Rails.
- Understanding and integrating a broad range of platforms (Google Analytics), CMSs (Wordpress & NationBuilder), and feature integrations (Zapier, Action Network).
- Scoping and building samples, docs, and developer content.
- · Collaborating and cultivating ambitious pitches with the Creative and Strategy Teams to continuously present clients with new products, concepts and more effective workflows.

DIRECTOR OF GLOBAL IMPACT

Tourism Cares (Sept 2018 - Oct 2021)

- Managed 160+ external partnerships with travel & tech brands corporate social responsibility, sustainability and DEI strategies.
- Speaker: NY Time Travel Show 2020, TravelCon Boston.
- DEI leadership featured in: The Washington Post

DIRECTOR OF DEVELOPMENT

G Adventures | Planeterra (July 2012 - Sept 2018)

- Worked cross-functionally with Software team to develop mobile fundraising app for consumer audience.
- Oversaw \$1.5M budget and planning process, increased donor revenue by 19% in one calendar year.
- Managed and mentored a globally-dispersed team of 4.